freelife.com 2013-09-23

# FreeLife Privacy Policies

FreeLife Privacy Policies
This Privacy Policy applies to the activities of FreeLife International, Inc. We appreciate
the trust you place in FreeLife, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the
security of your personal information. Our privacy policy describes the information we
collect and how we use it.
Your Consent
By using FreeLife website facilities and/or continuing to order products and services by
facsimile or telephone, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information
as detailed in this privacy policy.
Information We Share with Others and Your Privacy Rights
We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including without
limitation, credit card processing, IT consulting, printing, shipping, internet services, e-
commerce, off-site storage, public and media relations. We will provide these companies
with only the information they need to perform their services and ensure that they adhere
to strict privacy guidelines and do not keep this information or use it for any unauthorised
purposes. Generally, such companies are prohibited from sharing this information with
anyone other than FreeLife.
On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in
response to a court order, as required by tax laws, or when required by law to do so. We
may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation.
We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or
commercial purposes.
Your information may also be disclosed to FreeLife's related businesses and to any actual
or potential successor to any of these businesses.
Information We Collect
To best serve your needs, we will, from time to time, collect certain information from
you. We will only collect information where it is necessary to perform our services. The
information we collect may include, your name, address, telephone number, email
address, social security number, corporate information, including the entity’s tax id
number, credit card information, date of birth, testimonials, your sales history with us,
and other information we may request from you from time to time. Personal information
will be collected at various times including, if you:
         Apply to become a Marketing Executive
         Register as a Customer
         Order or reorder products by telephone or on our website
         Write an e-mail or letter to FreeLife
                                            -1-

       Sign up for the Advantage Customer Program
       Submit a testimonial to FreeLife
       Return an item or make an exchange
       Attend a FreeLife Event
       Participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event
       Contact our Customer Service department
       Navigate the website
       Register on our websites
       Request information about your FreeLife business
Using Information We Collect
We want to provide you with the best possible internet experience and fulfill your orders
exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we will only use your information to,
provide our services including, without limitation, to:
       Process your order
       Provide the products and services you request
       Send you promotional offers
       Identify your product and service preferences
       Customize our communications to you
       Issue commission payments
       Provide information concerning products you have purchased
       Provide information about your FreeLife business, including, but not limited to,
       issuing 1099 forms on an annual basis
       Improve our product selection and customer service
       Share your positive product testimonials with others
       Include your name, stories, testimonials and images in FreeLife publications and
       literature or other media, on FreeLife operated websites, at FreeLife events, on
       FreeLife CDs and DVDs, in any other FreeLife communications to our Marketing
       Executives or others, or as otherwise deemed useful or appropriate by FreeLife.
Cookies
FreeLife uses cookies on our websites. A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your
web browser on your computer. Cookies allow us to enhance, personalize, and track your
online experience, so that the information you receive is more relevant to you. This
technology will allow you to move faster through our website once the information is in
our database since you do not have to re-enter the same information or log in each time
you enter the site.
How We Use Email
When you provide us your email address, you may receive emails from us. E-mails may
be sent in order to assist us in processing your order, respond to a request, provide
customer service or inform you about products, services or promotional materials. It is
                                          -2-

our intent to send promotional e-mails only to those persons who wish to receive them.
We provide instructions on how to unsubscribe in our e-mails. Marketing Executives
during the term of their agreement with FreeLife will not be allowed to unsubscribe to
certain transactional e-mails, e.g., ship confirmation e-mails.
Links to Other Sites
We may provide links on our websites to other sites. These sites operate independently of
FreeLife and have established their own privacy and security policies. We encourage you
to review these policies at any site you visit.
Updating or Reviewing Your Information
You may review or update your Marketing Executive and Customer information (name,
address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, etc.) by clicking on “Go
To My FreeLife Office” on www.freelife.com or calling Customer Service.
Other personal information can be accessed and amended by contacting our privacy
officer at privacy@freelife.com.
Password and log-in security
For the purposes of accessing some areas of our website you will be supplied with a user
name and password. You are responsible for the security and confidentiality of your
password and log-in information.
Security
FreeLife is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. It is our
intent to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have
collected from you. We use a variety of current technologies and processes for protection
of information we collect, and we limit the information we provide to third parties.
When you make a purchase or submit a document on our website, your transactional
information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format.
Overseas Transfers
Your information may be stored by or on behalf of a member of the FreeLife group on
equipment outside of the United States.
Privacy of Children on Our Web Site
Our Web site is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 18. We do not
knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of 18
                                            -3-

Policy Changes
From time to time, we may use Marketing Executive or Customer information for
unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information
practices change, we will post these changes in our website. We encourage you to review
our privacy policy periodically
Contact Us
We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please
contact us at privacy@freelife.com
                                         -4-
